[
    {
        "lessonId": "Basic Verbs",
        "title": "Basic Verbs",
        "exercises": [
  {
    "front": "to go",
    "back": "ذَهَبَ || يَذْهَبُ",
    "back_hint": "dhahaba || yadhhabu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to want",
    "back": "أرَادَ || يُرِيدُ",
    "back_hint": "ʾaraada || yuriidu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to eat",
    "back": "أَكَلَ || يَأْكُلُ",
    "back_hint": "ʾakala || yaʾkulu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to hear / to listen",
    "back": "إسْتَمَعَ || أَسْتَمِعُ",
    "back_hint": "istamaʿa || ʾastamiʿu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to read",
    "back": "قَرَأَ || يَقْرَأُ",
    "back_hint": "qaraʾa || yaqraʾu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to teach",
    "back": "دَرَّسَ || يُدَرِّسُ",
    "back_hint": "darrasa || yudarrisu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to sleep",
    "back": "نَامَ || يَنَامُ",
    "back_hint": "naama || yanaamu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to wake up",
    "back": "إستيقَظَ || أَسْتَيْقِظُ",
    "back_hint": "istayqaẓa || ʾastayqiẓu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to run",
    "back": "رَكَضَ || يَرْكُضُ",
    "back_hint": "rakaDa || yarkuDu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to study",
    "back": "ذَاكَرَ || يُذَاكِرُ",
    "back_hint": "dhaakara || yudhaakiru"
  },
  {
    "front": "to watch",
    "back": "شَاهَدَ || يُشَاهِدُ",
    "back_hint": "shaahada || yushaahidu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to work / to make",
    "back": "عَمِلَ || يَعْمَلُ",
    "back_hint": "ʿamila || yaʿmalu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to remember",
    "back": "تَذَكَّرَ || يَتَذَكَّرُ",
    "back_hint": "tadhakkara || yatadhakkaru"
  },
  {
    "front": "to write",
    "back": "كَتَبَ || أَكْتُبُ",
    "back_hint": "kataba || ʾaktubu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to travel",
    "back": "سَافَرَ || يُسَافِرُ",
    "back_hint": "saafara || yusaafiru"
  },
  {
    "front": "to drink",
    "back": "شَرِبَ || يَشْرَبُ",
    "back_hint": "shariba || yashrabu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to memorize",
    "back": "حَفِظَ || يَحْفَظُ",
    "back_hint": "HafiZa || yaHfaZu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to ask",
    "back": "سَأَلَ || يَسْأَلُ",
    "back_hint": "saʾala || yasʾalu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to take",
    "back": "أَخَذَ || يَأْخُذُ",
    "back_hint": "ʾakhadha || yaʾkhudhu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to understand",
    "back": "فَهِمَ || يَفْهَمُ",
    "back_hint": "fahima || yafhamu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to live",
    "back": "سَكَنَ || يَسْكُنُ",
    "back_hint": "sakana || yaskunu"
  },
  {
    "front": "to stay",
    "back": "بَقِيَ || يَبْقَى",
    "back_hint": "baqiya || yabqaa"
  }
]   }
]